<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tripper\'s Trip</string>
    <string name="purpose">The intention of developing Tripper’s Trip is there is no need of hire any guide,as this is enough to guide you at new places.it will never let you alone so one can easily find or check where to go,what to do in new states. Instead of doing timewaste while searching on websites.</string>
    <string name="aboutus">Tripper’s Trip is a based on the Tour Guide mobile app that facilitates the all the information about the each state’s Attraction (best place to visit) alongwith relavent information about the Attractions.(for i.e. Name of the attraction,best time to vist,how to reach there,Tickets,Descriptions,Images).</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password reset email</string>
    <string name="remove_user">Remove user</string>
    <string name="new_pass">New Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Firebase</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Get registered in Firebase now!</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered. Login Me!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back"><![CDATA[<< Back]]></string>
    <string name="hint_new_email">New Email</string>
    <string name="btn_change">Change</string>
    <string name="btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">We just need your registered Email Id to sent you password reset instructions.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom_navi">BottomNavi</string>
    <!--new -->
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bnavigation">BnavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="action_deep_link">
        com.delaroystudios.appinvites.DEEP_LINK_ACTION
    </string>
    <string name="invite">Send Invitations!</string>
    <string name="welcome">App Invite\nQuickstart</string>
    <string name="referrer_hint">Deep link not provided</string>
    <string name="deep_link_default">Deep link not set</string>
    <string name="invite_friends">Invite Friends</string>

    <string name="invitation_title">Trippers App Invite Invitation Link</string>
    <string name="invitation_message">If you like to travel in India,then this app is the best place for you !</string>
    <string name="invitation_deep_link">http://example.com/offer/five_dollar_offer</string>
    <string name="invitation_custom_image">https://www.google.com/images/branding/googlelogo/2x/googlelogo_color_272*92dp.png</string>
    <string name="invitation_cta">Install !</string>
    <string name="invitation_subject">Try this great app!</string>
    <string name="deep_link_fmt" formatted="false">Deep Link:%s</string>
    <string name="invitation_id_fmt" formatted="false">Invitation ID:%s</string>
    <string name="sent_invitation_fmt" formatted="false">Sent %d invitations</string>
    <string name="send_failed">Sending Invitation Failed</string>
    <string name="invite_dialog_title">You got an Invitation!</string>
    <string name="google_play_service_error">Google play service error</string>
    <string name="custom_invite">Custom Invite</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- HISTORY HERE -->

    <string name="speaker">Getting Bored ?? While Reading\nbelow there is a listener,all you have to do is just tap on an icon!</string>
    <string name="histry">Uttarakhand - Simply Heaven\nNestled in the lap of the Himalayas, Uttarakhand is one of the most beautiful northern states of India that enthralls everyone with its spectacularly scenic landscapes. Charming hill stations juxtaposed against snow-capped peaks, quaint villages along winding mountain roads, serpentine rivers carving their way through hills, world renowned conservation parks like ‘Jim Corbett Tiger National Park’ and ‘Asan Wetland Conservation Reserve’, world heritage sites like ‘Valley of Flowers’ and ‘Nanda Devi Biosphere Reserve’, waterfalls hurtling down slopes and serene lakes shimmering amidst beautiful towns-thats,uttrakhand for you!</string>
    <string name="andra">Andhra Pradesh has a variety of tourist attractions including beaches, hills, caves, wildlife, forests As a tourist, one may want to explore places with rich history; high spiritual definition; profuse natural splendors and remarkable culture and trust us Andhra Pradesh offer just that! The land of Nizams, Pearls Kalamkari, Kondapalli Toys, Scrumptious Food and Amiable People, Andhra Pradesh is certainly a destination that needs to be explored on India tour</string>
    <string name="ggg">Shying away in the North eastern corner of India, Arunachal Pradesh though may be an introvert when it comes to tourism, is a land of abundant travel opportunities. Adorned with unspoilt landscape, this Northeast state of India is a place that every nature lover and explorer should visit. A treasure trove of culture, nature’s beauty, rich history and warm people, Arunachal is truly a land that you cannot afford to miss.
visit arunachal for Offbeat getaway, nature’s beauty, trekking, rafting, camping, birdwatching, tribal tours, root bridges, wildlife, motor biking, history, photography.</string>
    <string name="assam">Assam is one of the eight states in the Northeastern part of India. It is comprised mostly of the valleys of Brahmaputra and Barak. Assam and the rest of the Northeastern states are connected to the rest of the country via the Siliguri Corridor or the Chickens Neck, a 22-kilometre small strip of land in West Bengal. Its other name is the Gateway to the Northeast, as it is the main connection to reach the other states in the Northeastern part of the country. The state also shares an international border with Bhutan and Bangladesh. The people, culture and traditions of Assam are similar to that of the South Eastern countries.</string>
    <string name="br">Bihar is nestled on the banks of the holy river Ganga in the eastern part of India.The state shares its borders with Bengal,Orissa,Madhya Pradesh, Uttar Pradesh and Nepal. Bihar derives its name from a word Vihara that means monastery since the place in the past was a major learning centre of Buddhism. Ruled over by many great empires,it is renowned for its glorious past.Every nook and corner of this sacred land is dotted with historical monuments and Buddhist monasteries.Bihar is also renowned for its religious places.There are many Hindu,Buddhist,Jain,Muslim and Sikh shrines,which abound this ancient land.Some of the noteworthy Bihar travel destinations are Nalanda,Rajgir,Bodh Gaya,Patna,Vaishali,Vikramshila and Pawapuri.</string>
    <string name="chakkis"></string>
    <string name="chhatis">Bordered by Orissa on the east, Madhya Pradesh on the west, Bihar, Jharkhand and Uttar Pradesh on the north and Andhra Pradesh on the south, Chhattisgarh was formed on November 1, 2000, as Indias 26th state, carved out of Madhya Pradesh. This historic land affirms its mention as Dakshin Kosala in ancient texts, literary works, inscriptions, and accounts of foreign travelers.
    chhattisgarh is believed to be the place where Lord Rama spent some part of his exile. A tribal-dominated state, Chhattisgarh is an exquisitely scenic, covered with dense forest and crisscrossed by two mighty rivers, Indravati and Mahanadi. Ancient underground caves and gurgling waterfalls dot the breathtaking landscape. Incredible natural beauty blended with rich cultural heritage make Chhattisgarh one of the most promising tourist destinations of India.</string>
    <string name="delhi">Delhi is the capital city of India and is regarded as the heart of the nation.The city is popular for its enriched culture and heritage.The city hosts some famous historical monuments and is developing with the passing of time.The influence of religious diversity can be seen in the city along with the cultural impact of the Mughal, the ancient Indian and the British. There are many beautiful gardens in the city, away from pollution and busy city life that provide opportunities to walk leisurely in the midst of greenery.The capital city is divided into two sections popularly known as Purani Dilli or Old Delhi and Nayi Dilli or New Delhi. Old Delhi is popular for its ancient culture and monuments along with its overcrowded gastronomical lanes.</string>
    <string name="goa">Goa is a state full of loveliness.There is beauty sprinkled over every aspect of it.Some part of this state was under Portuguese rule for some time so we will be going to see the never-seen-before blend of Indian and Portuguese culture on this tour.Embark on this trip with us exploring the architectural splendour and historical grandeur of Goa.Enjoy the beaches of Goa bathed in the bright light of warm sun! This will be a reposeful experience for you altogether because you sun bathe yourself looking at the crystal clear blue waters touching the beach sand.</string>
    <string name="gujarat">Gujarat has always been a major centre for the Jains and some of its most interesting locations are the Jain Temple centres at Palitana and Girnar Hills. Besides the Jain temples, the state’s major attractions include the only habitat of the Asiatic Lions in India (Gir Forests), a desert ride at the Wild Ass Sanctuary and the beautiful Indo-Saracenic Architecture of Ahmedabad. The colourful tribal villages of Kutch make a visit unforgettable.
Aavo Padharo, words of welcome in the language of Gujarat because it is here that these words ring truly and the guest is God and the people of Gujarat are gregariously friendly,inviting and will entice you to come again and again.</string>
    <string name="hayrana">The name Haryana means the abode of God.It is a blend of two Sanskrit words ‘Hari’ which means God and ‘ayana’ meaning home.It is a land where guests are treated equal to god.Haryana represents the face of modern India.The one which is heralding the future yet prides itself of being rooted in its magnificent culture.Today Haryana is positioned among one of the wealthiest and most economically developed regions in South Asia.Haryana is a vivid kaleidoscope of diverse landscapes, showcasing magnificent archaeology and celebrating art and culture. A state that has transcended on a journey and preserved the best of both worlds–the footprints of the bygone era and futuristic vision.</string>
    <string name="himachal">Himachal tourism is all about exploring the unexplored natural jewels of beauty that adorn the land of Himachal Pradesh. The state has its very own char that beguiles travelers to explore the north-Indian hotspot. Dotted with numerous hill stations and sights of attraction that boasts snow-covered mountains, lush green valleys, oak and pine covered forests, pristine environs and natural peace. The state beholds such a majestic charm that you will never feel like leaving. It is the best way to seek a getaway from the humdrums of your city life and rejuvenate your mind body and soul.</string>
    <string name="jammu">Popularly known as the "Paradise on the Earth" the state is world famous for its scenic splendour, snow-capped mountains, plentiful wildlife, exquisite monuments, hospitable people and local handicraft
Jammu and Kashmir is the northernmost state of India locked in Himalayan Mountains. Jammu and Kashmir is home to several Valleys such as the Kashmir Valley, Tawi Valley, Chenab Valley, Punch Valley, Sindh Valley and Lidder Valley. Some major tourist attractions in Jammu and Kashmir are Srinagar, the Mughal Gardens, Gulmarg, Pahalgam, Patnitop, Jammu, and Ladakh. Some areas require a special permit for non-Indians to visit. A beautiful place with lakes,mountains and valleys. A great destination to spend some time and refresh mood.</string>
    <string name="jharkhand">While it is on the Chhotanagpur plateau, one of the oldest land formations in the world, Jharkhand the 28th state of India. With nearly one-third of its total area under forest cover, Jharkhand is rightfully called the “land of forests”.

The lush green forests, rivers and waterfalls of this primeval land are home to many kinds of spectacular flora and fauna. Age-old tribes are the main inhabit of this wonderful land, the state is also a hubs of industry, commerce and education. A treasure-trove of minerals comprises 40 per cent of the mineral wealth of the country ranking first in the production of coal, mica and iron and helps in making Jharkhand one of the richest state of india in natural resources.</string>
    <string name="karnataka">Karnataka is a tapestry of colours, cultures, flavours, landscapes, timelessness and heart stopping beauty. It’s a place where vibrant worlds seamlessly meld into one another every few hundred kilometers. Sedate plains suddenly rise to dizzying mist covered hilly heights, and then plunge with careless abandon in a white-watered freefall to become languid rivers that flow past cities where time has stopped altogether. And cities where time rushes a relentless rush to keep up with the world; cities that sometimes escape into the deep quietude of thick forests and sometimes, stretches their arms wide open to embrace the sea.</string>
    <string name="kerala">Wedged between the Western Ghats on the East and the Arabian Sea on the West, the narrow strip of land known as Kerala is a destination of a lifetime.The timeless beauty of the palm fringed beaches of Kovalam and Varkala, the majesty of the undulating hills of Munnar and Vagamon, the serenity of the pristine backwaters of Kumarakom and Kuttanad and the enchanting woods and forests of Thekkady and Silent Valley will have you bowled over.That such a small terrain can hold diverse geographical features and cultures is a wonder in itself.</string>
    <string name="mp">Madhya Pradesh can be described as the best state of the nation when it comes to the diversity of its tourism destinations.Madhya Pradesh is know as the "Heart of India' not only beca​use of its location on the map, but also because of the lot many things it offers.; it has been home to cultural and spiritual heritage of almost all the religions. Innumerable monuments,intricately carved temples, stupas, forts and palaces are dotted all over the State. The state is home to three UNESCO World Heritage Sites namely Sanchi, Bhimbetka and Khajuraho.</string>
    <string name="mumbai">The City that Never Sleeps,The City of Dreams and The City of Seven Islands are just a few of the epithets used to describe the wonderful city of Mumbai or Bombay, as it was known before.Located along the Konkan coast and home to Indias film industry,the capital of Maharashtra and the financial capital of India is multi-faceted and provides a lot of exciting experiences. And it demands to be experienced.
The most striking feature about Mumbai is its rich diversity. The rich and the poor, movie stars and daily wage labourers, dazzlingly tall skyscrapers and large slum areas, grand cosmopolitan malls and local street bazaars all exist side-by-side in this city. The city of Mumbai offers everything to the bustling crowds that make up its heartbeat-beautiful lakes, beaches, parks and both impressive modern and historically significant architecture.</string>
    <string name="manipur">The jewel city of India, Manipur is listed among one of the most beautiful places of India where Mother Nature has been extra generous in her bounty. Least touched and least discovered, Manipur promises to be the great tourist discovery as the state offer endless enjoyment and pleasure with its exotic landscape, undulating hills, green valleys, blue lakes and dense forests. The Keibul Lamjao National Park in Manipur is the only floating national park in the world,Richly endowed with the natural beauty of waterfalls, lakes, streams, evergreen forests surrounded by nine sub-Himalayan ranges that attract the tourists from all over the world, Manipur is beautiful, calm and serene with its most ecstatic simplicity. Its greenery with the moderate climate makes it attractive to tourists.</string>
    <string name="meghalaya">Meghalaya, the abode of clouds, is one of the most beautiful states in the North-East India offering a variety of sights, activities, food and festivals to the tourists. Well known for Cherapunjji, the place which receives one of the maximum rainfall in the world, Meghalaya can mesmerise you with its hills, valleys, lakes, caves and waterfalls which give it a beautiful look when covered with beautiful clouds.The land of simple yet so colourful and entertaining people, Meghalaya is inhabited by three tribes Garo, Khasi and Jayantia which add to the richness of the state as all of the three tribes have their languages, religion, festivals, costumes, cuisines and dances!</string>
    <string name="mizoram">The moderate climate of Mizoram, comfortable even in summer, makes it a comfortable destination for all the tourists whereas the vast culture and grand festivals od the state have a unique irresistible charm which can not be explained, said or read, it can only be felt once you are in there in the peaceful, serene land of Mizoram surropunded by green forests adn high hills taking you to a different world.
              Mizoram offers you a calm, serene atmosphere with exciting outdoor activities in the beautiful lush green surroundings which keeps you close to the peaceful nature.</string>
    <string name="nagaland">Inhabited by the tribes who are very protective towards their culture and identity, Nagaland is another name for beauty and bounty. Colorful costumes, spicy cuisines, pleasant weather, traditional villages, beautiful dance forms and lyrical songs are all that define the north-eastern state of Nagaland.Japfu Peak, Dzukou Valley, Shilloi Lake are some of the places for nature lovers while the villages of Nagaland add rustic charm to your trip. Like other north-eastern states, Nagaland is also rich in culture with the variety of tribes spreading colours in it. The artistic skills of local people will not only amaze you but excite you to learn the weaving and carving which is simply mesmerising.</string>
    <string name="orissa">The historical state of Orissa is situated amidst beautiful lush green mountains of the Eastern Ghats. This historical land is bounded by the states of Andhra Pradesh, Chhattisgarh, Jharkhand and West Bengal. Orissa is blessed its palm-fringed beaches, shimmering lakes, serpentine rivers, mighty waterfalls, forest-clad blue hills of Eastern Ghats, which are home to rich flora and fauna that impress and lure tourists from all over the world. Orissa is famous for its fairs festivals, stone carving, silver filigree, applique work, exquisite handicrafts, and beautiful textiles. Dotted with numerous architecturally celebrated temples, sacred shrines, and historical monuments, Orissa is considered India’s one of the most hidden splendid cultural landscapes.</string>
    <string name="punjb">Punjab, the land of five rivers and astounding cultural history is located in the north west of India. Popularly referred to as the "Granary of India", it is the second largest producer of major agricultural products in the country. Punjab is renowned for its sports and hosiery goods industry. It is one of the most prosperous states of India in terms of infrastructure and per capita income. The charming cities and towns of Punjab are dotted with numerous ancient monuments, gurudwaras, temples, ashrams, serene lakes, sacred shrines, museums, and wildlife sanctuaries, which are home to many rare species of animals and migratory birds.</string>
    <string name="sikkim">Under the starry sky exists a paradise that is full of warm-hearted people and fairytale destinations. Ornamenting the right shoulder of India, Sikkim is a hideout from the hullabaloo of chaotic urban life. Last to be added as a part of Northeastern Region, Sikkim vouches for an incredible holiday experience that is an assortment of adventure, opulent history, nature’s beauty, and heart melting culture. Music to the ears of holidaymakers, this Northeastern piece of melody is where rejuvenation awaits you amidst scintillating high altitude lakes, green sprawls, gorgeous waterfalls and meandering rivers; and where spirituality and peace of mind find you at serene monasteries; and celebration of a plethora of fairs and festivals makes you fall in love.</string>
    <string name="raj">Jaw-dropping forts and havelis; commendable folk music; myriad tales of chivalry and mouth-watering food welcome you to the culturally wealthy state of Rajasthan. The land of turbans, moustache, ghoonghat and camels, Rajasthan is an unparalleled tourist destination when it comes to culture and heritage tourism in India. Home to famed tigers like Machhali, the desert state also boasts memorable wildlife adventure. Brace yourself for heart-warming hospitality; luxurious stays and unforgettable experiences.</string>
    <string name="tamil">A land of cultural and religious heritage,Tamil Nadu offers every chance to the tourist or pilgrims to be enchanted with the vast plethora of history and beauty that it has.It is a blend of modern and ancient, that makes Tamil Nadu a beautiful destination to explore our past cultural heritage with all the amenities of the present.Lying along the Bay of Bengal,Tamil Nadu with its glorious history spanning thousands of years and today is paving the way to becoming one of the promising states of the country. This state has seen the rise and fall of many Dynasties of Cholas, Cheras, Pallavas, and each dynasty has enriched the place with its own customs and traditions.</string>
    <string name="tripura">Tripura the hidden gem of lndia lies tucked away in the north East corner, bordered by Bangladesh on all three sides, except the East where it shares its borders with Assam and Mizoram. A land of beautiful green mountains and dense forests, criss-crossed by numerous rivers and lakes.The third smallest state in India and one of the ‘Seven Sisters’ of the North East, Tripura is geographically a little remote. It however offers many surprises for the traveller who is willing to traverse its less trodden roads. From wildlife sanctuaries, mesmerizing architectural wonders of palaces, temples and other shrines, to pulsating lakes and more, Tripura offers a lot to the avid traveller.</string>
    <string name="telan">The state of Telangana came into being on June 2, 2014, when it broke away from its parent state Andhra Pradesh to become the 29th state of India. It was named Telangana to represent the Telugu speaking region, as distinguished from the Marathawada region of Andhra Pradesh.The state is historically best known for the Nizams of Hyderabad who ruled in the 14th century making it a princely state.The state lies mainly in the Deccan plateau region and is drained by two major rivers Godavari and Krishna, besides some more minor rivers.The state has a deep historical connect, a rich culture and a treasure trove of tourist attractions as monuments, forts, temples, waterfalls, sacred groves, national parks and sanctuaries.</string>
    <string name="up">Home to one of the Seven Wonders of the World and flaunting exquisite arts like the handicrafts and jewellery Uttar Pradesh is a bountiful state and an utterly religious one.
Uttar Pradesh is the home to some of the most beautiful monuments and cultural sights in India.With massive royal influence in the fields of dance and music and arts, this state is home to one of the first classical dances of India, Kathak.The state is also known for its Nawabi style in food, can advertise fantastic street food like the samosa and kachori as well as the royal meaty feasts and kebabs.</string>
    <string name="kolkata">Labeled as the City of Joy, the Cultural capital of India, Kolkata (formerly known as Calcutta)is a city with character and remnants of British Raj visible in its Victorian-style architecture,trams and feel. It is one of the most densely populated cities in India With a heritage as dense and the population, this city along the banks of river Ganga is known for its culture, people, food, music, literature and the movies.
Some other interesting places are the Eden Garden, Bellur Math Temple, Aurobindo Ashram, Birla Planetarium, Nicco Park, Marble Palace and Howrah Bridge. The famous Durga Puja in October draws many people to the city. Kolkata is also famous for one of Indias oldest brothels called the Sonagachi.</string>
</resources>
